[microphone feedback]
[♪ opening theme music playing]
FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
[blade swooshing]
[♪ music swells]
[Gaeun panting]
[panting, breath trembling]
- [stick taps twice]
- What are you doing?
[Gaeun, breath trembling]
Gaeun, what's wrong?
[breathing heavily]
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
I'm the lead dancer.
- [barks]
- [K9 handler] Shush. [mutters]
SONG GAEUN
I'm the lead dancer. [gasping shakily]
[Dahye] Hey...
[♪ music swells]
- [sharp swoosh, slash]
- [shrieks, echoing]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
[Gaeun gasping shakily]
[breathing heavily]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[panting, gasping]
[sword clatters]
[gasping]
[panting, gasping]
[♪ music swells]
[Gaeun continues panting]
[♪ music fades]
[siren blaring]
[students whispering anxiously]
EPISODE 10
Is the culprit among them?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
How did it go?
We found some traces here and there.
But we can't narrow down a suspect.
Too many people use this space.
- Okay. Thank you for coming.
- [K9 handler] Sure.
What happened?
A curse pouch was found in Seyeon's bag,
and it had drugs inside.
Drugs?
Gaeun was hallucinating
because of the same drug.
Are you saying one of my students
did something like that?
Don't tell the students anything just yet.
[♪ music fades]
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
[Junyoung] This is
commonly known as "Ruby."
Just touching it can make you hallucinate.
It's sold anonymously on the dark web,
so they can't identify the buyers.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
CONTACT WITH NARCOTIC SUBSTANCE
HALLUCINATION
REPEATEDLY STRUCK LEGS
So Seyeon touched those rubies
and died from an asthma attack?
Yes.
They may not have intended it,
but it ended in a murder.
But even so,
could a high school student get
their hands on a drug like this?
It's not impossible.
The dark web doesn't have an age limit.
[Isoo] I don't understand
cursing someone
just to steal the lead role.
I heard the arts festival
is a pretty big deal.
All the famous
dance companies will be there.
We can't trace the drug,
so we'll have to go after the curse pouch.
Check the footage from the Witch's Shop.
Make a list of everyone
who bought a curse pouch.
Got it.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[keyboard clacks]
Detective Joo.
A student bought one
the day before the incident.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
That's Hayun.
[♪ music fades]
Hi, Hayun.
Can we talk for a moment?
[Isoo] Hayun, what will you have?
I'm fine.
You should eat something.
Then I'll get the Chicken Bacon Mini Wrap.
Okay. Italian B.M.T. for you,
Detective Joo?
Yeah. Coffee, too.
Coffee? What about you, Hayun?
I'll just drink water.
No. Jin Isoo is buying today.
Want anything more to eat, huh?
You must be startled
after what happened with Gaeun.
Yeah, why did she do that?
I'm not sure.
Have your friends said anything about it?
They said maybe she lost it
after getting the lead.
Ah. [chuckles softly]
[Isoo] Mmm.
[♪ jaunty, dramatic music playing]
All right.
Here, drink this.
Coffee for Detective Joo.
Let's eat.
[softly] Mmm...
Mmm!
It's good, right?
- Right?
- Yes.
You girls are always on a diet, huh.
You need to eat well for your arm to heal.
Can you pick that up for me?
[♪ music fades]
You're right.
I put this inside Seyeon's bag.
Gaeun, too?
Gaeun? What about Gaeun?
But how did you know?
Mmm.
The security camera.
[chuckles nervously, swears softly]
So, what about it?
[wrapper crumpling]
Seyeon died because of that pouch.
Is this a real curse?
I was only messing around.
No.
There was a drug inside
that causes hallucinations.
What?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
What are you talking about?
Uh, if, by any chance,
you put it in as a joke--
What are you talking about?
Do you think I'm crazy?
It really wasn't me.
I did it because I was annoyed.
Where would I even get drugs?
If I got caught, I'd be expelled.
And everyone at school does this.
They send curses
to people they don't like.
The principal knows as well.
Some kids had theirs confiscated.
The principal knows, too?
Yes. Go ask her.
When did you put the pouch in?
During the afternoon class
on the day Seyeon died.
CHANGING ROOM
[♪ suspenseful music continues]
MOON SEYEON
I got really scared
when she actually died.
[♪ music fades]
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
KIM HAYUN
I don't think Hayun is the culprit.
Detective Choi.
Let's see the hallway
outside the studio that afternoon.
Okay.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
Did Hayun just put the pouch in?
- Wait.
- [keyboard clacks]
What's this?
[Junyoung] Principal Jeong Joohee?
The principal slipped in the drugs?
The principal killed Seyeon?
She has no reason to.
She said she gave Seyeon
the lead because of her asthma.
She might've gone in to get something.
Anyone could have gotten to Seyeon's bag.
If all those students
are giving each other curses,
how can we narrow down the suspects?
[sighs softly]
Did you find anything on Seyeon's phone?
Nothing significant.
[sighs softly]
I CURSE YOU, MOON SEYEON
DIE, DIE!
By the way,
if she wanted to curse someone,
why not write their name?
Why just write that she cursed them?
Maybe she wanted to curse multiple people.
Like the ones responsible for her death.
But there wasn't anyone like that.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
Huh?
[♪ suspenseful music plays, swells]
I CURSE YOU
[in English] What the...
[in Korean] Oh, my God!
[♪ music fades]
Hey, come here.
- What is it?
- I think I'm a freaking genius.
Look.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
JEONG JOOHEE
[gasps]
"Jeong Joohee"?
Maybe what Yuna actually wanted
to write was "Jeong Joohee."
Jeong Joohee was the one
who killed Baek Yuna?
She made her kill herself?
But why?
She even received money
from Baek Yuna's parents.
Jeong Joohee is suspicious, though.
Right. She knew about the curse pouch,
but pretended not to.
What's this?
Have you never seen it before?
It's a trend among the students.
It's a curse pouch.
The students carry this around?
Gaeun also said something, too.
But Seyeon told me
the principal has no choice
but to pick her for the lead.
Seyeon didn't have the money to bribe her,
so why did Jeong Joohee have
no choice but to pick her as the lead?
[♪ music swells]
JEONG JOOHEE
[♪ music fades]
[Isoo] Ma'am,
it seems the principal
was very fond of Seyeon.
She was.
She came to see me.
Principal Jeong Joohee came to see you?
[Grandma] Yes.
She said she felt bad.
[♪ suspenseful, pulsating music playing]
She brought that with her.
Thank you for coming all the way
to this humble place, Principal Jeong.
You must be heartbroken.
But she said
she had left something with Seyeon.
[drawer opens, rummaging]
[drawer closes]
[drawer opens]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[rummaging continues]
She searched Seyeon's room?
[Grandma] Yes.
But I don't think she found it.
She just left.
[♪ music resumes tempo]
And you have no idea what it was?
No, I wouldn't know.
[♪ music fades]
Ma'am.
[exhales softly]
I figured you wouldn't have eaten.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
I don't know
if it's worth living like this.
I outlived my daughter,
and now I even lost
my poor granddaughter. [sobbing]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[shaman] An item with fur, about this big.
She left it behind.
Ma'am.
Is this your phone?
What's the matter?
The shaman said she saw this.
It used to be Seyeon's phone.
She gave it to me a few months ago.
May I take a look?
Of course.
- Feel free to.
- Okay.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
This is a video app.
Ma'am, do you know what this is?
I don't know any of that stuff.
Ah. I'm going to take a look.
- [Grandma] Okay.
- Thanks.
- [♪ music swells]
- [Isoo inhales sharply]
ALL VIDEOS
[♪ music slows, turns ominous]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[phone case snaps shut]
Ma'am.
Make sure you eat properly.
Please stay healthy.
We promise to catch the culprit
who did this to Seyeon.
Thank you.
[♪ music fades]
JUYEON ARTS HIGH SCHOOL
2025 JUYEON ARTS HIGH SCHOOL ARTS FESTIVAL
[indistinct chatter]
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
[spectral exhale]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
2025 JUYEON ARTS HIGH SCHOOL ARTS FESTIVAL
[indistinct chatter]
[Isoo] No more cursing each other.
You should all be
sharing good luck instead, okay?
- [students] Okay.
- [Isoo] Here.
[in English] Good luck.
[in Korean] Here you go.
Here you go.
We came to see the performance, too.
Sure.
I hope you enjoy the show.
Yes, I'm sure it'll be very enjoyable.
All right, you got this!
- We got this!
Everyone ready?
- Yes.
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[door closes]
[AV technician] Who are you?
Excuse me for a moment.
Ah, right.
[♪ music fades]
[footsteps approaching, heels clicking]
Thank you all for joining us at
the Juyeon Arts High School Arts Festival.
Juyeon Arts High School
has grown into a prestigious school
known for producing exceptional dancers,
and we owe much of that success
to one special person.
I'd like to introduce you all
to Principal Jeong Joohee,
who leads our school
with nothing but love for her students.
[all applauding, cheering]
Whoo!
[all applauding, cheering loudly]
[applauding, cheering fades]
I'd like to thank our distinguished guests
for taking the time to join us today.
Recently, a tragic event
befell our school.
Despite their grief, our students
worked hard to prepare this performance.
I would be grateful
if you could give them
your warmest support.
[all applauding]
[applauding fades]
WHEN A NAME BECOMES A GENRE OF ITS OWN
[♪ upbeat, dramatic music playing]
JEONG JOOHEE, THE DANCER
WHO HAS DEFINED AN ERA OF KOREAN DANCE
HER NAME IS NOW A DIRECTION
THE REASON KOREAN DANCE
KEPT MOVING FORWARD
NOW SHE FOCUSES ON NURTURING TALENT
[all applauding]
AN EDUCATOR OF BOTH DANCE AND CHARACTER
AN ICON SETTING THE STANDARD
FOR THE NEXT GENERATION
JUYEON ARTS HIGH SCHOOL
WILL CARRY ON HER LEGACY
- [video, music stop abruptly]
- [projector clicks]
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
[utility knife clicking]
- [slices]
- [all gasp]
[all murmuring anxiously]
[anxious murmuring intensifies]
Mr. Park, what's going on?
Turn that off right now!
- [radio clicks off]
- [audience exclaiming]
It's okay.
[audience gasping, exclaiming]
[mic thuds, whines]
[students scream]
[panting] Girls.
This isn't real.
It's all fake.
[audience murmuring anxiously]
[panting frantically]
[Juhee sighs, whimpers]
[audience continues murmuring]
[breath trembles] No.
It's all a lie.
You're a murderer.
It's on video.
What do you mean it's a lie?
[audience members jeering]
[gasping sharply, yelling]
I said, it's not true!
[♪ ominous music playing]
[spectral exhale]
[softly] Girls.
[whimpering shakily]
[gasping sharply]
[audience murmuring anxiously]
[♪ music swells]
[whimpering shakily, gasps]
[thuds]
[audience exclaiming]
[spectator] Shouldn't we
call an ambulance?
[all murmuring anxiously]
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
Why did you kill her?
Baek Yuna.
She didn't know her place.
[♪ music fades]
[Yuna] Ms. Jeong.
7 MONTHS AGO
Am I not talented?
[scoffs]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
What are you talking about?
You're exceptionally gifted.
Then why did you take money from my mom?
Did I get the lead because of the money?
You even told her
you'd get me into college no matter what.
That's not playing fair.
[scoffs softly]
Yuna.
Having money
is a talent.
You're probably too young to understand.
Playing fair?
That's all an illusion.
Nothing is fair in this world.
Everything's decided
the moment you're born.
Just like your genes.
You can't last in this industry
without money anyway.
So stop being so childish,
and just enjoy the benefits
of having wealthy parents, huh?
I don't want to.
What?
I want to be recognized for my own talent.
[scoffs softly]
What are you going to do about it?
Turn yourself in.
Otherwise, I'm going to report you myself.
[♪ music swells]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[♪ music fades]
[cell phone vibrating]
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
Yes, Ms. Ryu.
Hello, Principal Jeong.
Have you been well?
Yes.
I have the bag you mentioned last time.
I'll stop by to see you soon.
Ah.
Yes, all right.
[line disconnects]
[♪ tense, foreboding music continues]
You came to practice. [chuckles]
You changed your mind, right?
You made the right choice.
Acting all righteous
won't do you any good.
[♪ music fades]
I came to practice one last time.
One last time?
Turn yourself in by tomorrow.
I'm going to quit everything, too.
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[seat belt unbuckles]
[spectral exhale]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[clicking]
[♪ ominous sting]
[♪ soft, gentle music playing]
[spectral exhale]
[♪ woman vocalizing gently]
[♪ vocalizing, music fades]
[♪ gentle, melancholy music playing]
[sniffling, crying]
[sniffles, breath trembles]
Yuna.
I know how you feel. [inhales shakily]
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
[exhales softly]
It's all been so hard on you.
You haven't been able to sleep,
and I heard
you're even taking antidepressants.
[voice shaking] Ms. Jeong.
You love dancing.
How could you give it up, right?
I'm taking antidepressants because of you.
I've known for a while
that my mom gave you money.
I thought about looking the other way,
because my mom and I would
also be blamed if this got out.
[breathes shakily] Yuna.
This won't be for long.
If you just get through this,
you'll become the best dancer there is.
[♪ tense, melancholy music playing]
[Juhee's breath trembling]
I don't want to end up like you.
What?
Ms. Jeong.
dance was the one thing I loved most,
and you corrupted it.
Take back what you just said.
If you say you're sorry,
I'll forgive you just this once.
I'm...
giving you a chance.
No.
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
Let go.
[utility knife clicking]
[Juhee grunts]
[gasps incredulously, breathing heavily]
[utility knife clatters]
[breath trembling] Ms. Jeong.
[Juhee] Don't resent me.
You made me do this.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[breathing raggedly]
[♪ pulsating foreboding music playing]
[grunts, gasps]
[continues breathing raggedly]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[gasping sharply]
[groans softly]
[whimpers weakly]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
She's like this until the end.
[clicks tongue]
JEONG JOOHEE
[♪ music increases in tempo]
I CURSE YOU
- [♪ music resumes tempo]
- [Yuna] Mom, I'm sorry.
[♪ music fades]
[crying softly]
It was killing me, too.
Yuna haunted my dreams every night,
and I couldn't sleep.
No medication would work,
and I even turned to drugs because of her.
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
But then,
there was another student
who didn't know her place.
[glass clinks]
[exhales sharply]
[breathing deeply]
- [knock at door]
- [gasps softly]
[door opens]
[♪ music fades]
- Oh.
- [door closes]
It's you, Seyeon. What can I do for you?
I have something to tell you.
I'm a bit busy right now.
Let's talk another time.
This won't take long.
What is it? Make it quick.
I wish I could give you
a lot of money as well,
but my family isn't well-off.
I can't even afford private lessons.
So I was secretly recording
your tutoring sessions with Yuna.
[♪ ominous music playing]
- [utility knife slices]
- [Yuna gasps incredulously]
[utility knife clatters over recording]
[Yuna, breath trembling]
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
[sighs softly] You know,
I'd actually given up on everything.
Only five students can go to
Hankuk University from our department.
And they'll all be students
from rich, powerful families.
Whereas I have nothing.
But then this opportunity came along.
[chuckles nervously]
[stuttering] Seyeon.
Does anyone else know about this?
[chuckles] Of course not.
No one else can know.
I can't have you getting arrested.
Seyeon,
you can't do this. Delete that right now.
Can a teacher kill her student?
All you have to do
is favor me from now on.
Start by making me
the lead dancer in the festival.
Don't even think about trying anything.
I'm not like Yuna.
I won't be easy to deal with.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[scoffs]
I'll keep this nice and safe
so no one finds out.
Don't worry about that.
I'll delete it
once I get into Hankuk University.
[♪ music swells]
[door opens, closes]
[♪ music fades]
So I did exactly as Seyeon asked,
but the parents of the student originally
chosen for the lead kept calling me.
They kept hounding me
about how much Seyeon had paid me.
You even killed someone
after taking a bribe,
yet you accepted money again?
You think I asked for it?
They come to me on their own.
They come with designer bags and cash,
asking me to look after their kid.
Is that why you decided
to kill Seyeon as well?
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
[inhales sharply]
That wasn't my intention from the start.
I was...
just wondering what I should do,
then...
I went online to get some drugs.
JUYEON ARTS HIGH SCHOOL
[exhales softly]
GOT SOMETHING NEW, WANNA TRY?
WHAT IS IT?
SOMETHING THAT FEELS GOOD
JUST BY TOUCHING IT
BUT BAD FOR HEART CONDITION OR ASTHMA
[keyboard clacking]
WHY? WHAT HAPPENS?
WORST CASE, YOU DIE
[♪ ominous sting]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[door opens]
- [student 1] Hello.
- [student 2] Hello.
Warm up.
[sighs softly]
[♪ music turns ominous]
- [switch clicks]
- Warm up and start rehearsing.
- Yes, ma'am.
- [students] Yes, ma'am.
MOON SEYEON
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ ominous, ticking music playing]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
[spectral whoosh]
[spectral exhale]
[♪ percussive folk music playing]
[blade swooshing]
- [♪ music stops]
- [panting]
[♪ music turns ominous]
[Yuna] Seyeon.
Please... help me.
- [spectral exhale]
- [sword clatters]
Don't come any closer.
Stay away from me!
Seyeon, please help me.
[screaming]
[blunt thudding]
[continues screaming]
[gasping frantically, grunting]
[♪ music swells, fades]
- [wheezing heavily]
- [sword clatters]
[♪ soft, somber music playing]
[wheezing, choking]
[Isoo] You're the one who slipped
Gaeun the drugs as well, right?
To make it look like
an incident between the students.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
SONG GAEUN
[scoffs]
[♪ music fades]
You really are something else.
As a teacher,
you killed two of your students.
How can you live with that?
[inhales sharply] What else could I
have done? There was no other way.
[breath trembles]
They blackmailed me first,
so this was self-defense.
If you had just admitted your crime,
no one would have died.
[scoffs]
[♪ soft, suspenseful music playing]
Who in the world would do that?
[yelling] I have a name
and a reputation to uphold!
You're the one
who tarnished that reputation.
Now, people will remember you
not as the legend of Korean dance,
but as a murderer.
[sobbing softly]
MOON SEYEON, MAY YOU REST IN PEACE
[♪ somber, melancholy music playing]
WE WILL MISS YOU, SEYEON
[sniffling, sobbing]
[sniffles]
My poor child. [sobbing bitterly]
My poor child.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
PRINCIPAL JEONG JOOHEE
[shattering]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ gentle piano music playing]
CURSE CHARM
JUNYOUNG, KYUNGJIN
I CURSE YOU, BREAK UP
Where's everyone?
Off to meet their girlfriends. [sighs]
Such romantics, aren't they?
[chuckles softly]
Why don't us single folks
go get something to eat?
Shall we go somewhere I know?
It's Michelin-starred.
- Let's just go local. I'm hungry.
- [mouse clicking]
You must have
a bottomless pit for a stomach.
Wrap it up quickly.
Oh, I'm starving.
I just need to finish this.
[crunching]
Mmm! It's delicious.
- It's good, right?
- Yeah.
This is the best place around here.
Why go to a Michelin restaurant
when we have a place like this?
Hey, Michelin is Michelin, so...
[sighs in exasperation] Forget it.
Want a draft beer?
Yeah, sounds good.
Can we have two...
No, one glass of draft beer, please.
[server] Sure.
Mmm!
That's good.
By the way, that reed you gave me.
Yeah?
Apparently, they can't determine
the exact location with that,
because it's native to the west coast.
[♪ soft, suspenseful music playing]
What are you going to do about Seongwon?
I have someone watching him.
[♪ suspenseful, ticking music playing]
[Mr. Hwang] Welcome home, Young Master.
[door closes]
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
[keyboard clacking]
Thank you.
[cell phone vibrating]
PI JEONG MINJAE
Hello?
Yu Seongwon brought a woman to his studio.
I'll head there first.
Okay, we're on our way.
- [line disconnects]
- What's wrong?
Yu Seongwon brought a woman to his studio.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[Areum] Your studio is really nice.
[sighs] I wish I could work
in a studio like this.
You can work here anytime you want.
- Really?
- Of course.
[giggles excitedly]
If you can make it here.
[♪ ominous music playing]
- [camera shutter clicking]
- Why do you take photographs?
To feel you while I work.
Can I get a copy if they come out well?
[chuckles softly]
No.
What kind of artwork
are you going to make me into?
I'm not sure. [sighs softly]
I can't say I know you yet.
What do you like most?
I like painting the most.
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
I wish I could
spend just one month painting,
without worrying about money.
[scoffs]
That's no fun.
What's no fun?
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[liquid squirting]
- [camera shutter clicks]
- Talk about something else.
What was the worst thing you've ever done?
[chuckles softly] The worst thing?
[♪ music fades]
What about you?
The worst thing I've done?
[♪ ominous music playing]
You'd be shocked if you knew.
What was it?
I gave my father
a makeover.
Your father?
I put really heavy makeup on him.
[♪ music swells]
- [♪ music resumes tempo]
- Why?
Because I didn't like his expression.
[chuckles softly]
Didn't he tell you off?
He didn't say anything.
[exhales softly]
Want a glass of champagne?
[♪ ominous music continues]
[footsteps approaching]
Any movements?
Not yet.
Should we go in now?
No, let's just wait.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ ominous sting]
How do you want to die?
What?
Have you never thought about that?
[chuckles softly]
[♪ ominous sting]
Well,
I'd want to die painlessly and peacefully.
Peacefully?
[♪ gripping, ominous music playing]
That's nice, too.
Drink up.
[♪ ominous, ticking music playing]
[♪ music swells]
[car horn blaring]
- [♪ music fades]
- [car horn honking]
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
[car horn honking]
[car horn honking, blaring]
Young Master Isoo is here.
[sighs deeply]
[chuckles]
We have an unwanted guest.
Sorry to drop in so late. Can I come in?
- Oh. Yes, of course.
- Thanks.
[♪ music swells, fades]
Isoo!
What brings you here out of the blue?
I just remembered you said you liked this.
Here. We'll drink one bottle now.
Thank you.
You have a guest.
Ah, you must be his model.
[chuckles softly]
Yes. Aren't you Jin Isoo?
She knows me. She must be a fan.
Would you like a photo?
- Really?
- Yes.
All right.
- One, two, three.
- [camera shutter clicks]
Nice to meet you. What's your name?
Song Areum.
Areum.
Would you like to join us for a drink?
I made this.
No.
Uh...
Areum should probably get going.
Let's do this another time.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Areum] Ah.
[chuckles softly]
Okay, sure.
Mmm, then I'll have to call you a cab.
The premium kind. One second. Ah...
Your cab's here.
Wear your seatbelt.
- Okay.
- Right.
[exhales contentedly]
You look like a skilled driver.
Please take her home safely. Bye.
Seriously, what the heck?
What do you mean?
Come on, let's go have a drink.
Let's go.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Let's go!
- [♪ music resumes tempo]
- [Hyera panting] Wait.
I'm a detective.
[♪ music fades]
You were with Yu Seongwon, weren't you?
Yes.
What's going on?
Could I talk to you for a second?
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
I work part-time as a bartender.
I met him at the bar.
Did he ask you to be his model?
Yes.
But what's this all about?
Two of Yu Seongwon's models are missing.
What do you mean?
We're investigating those cases.
[♪ pulsating, suspenseful music playing]
No wonder.
He said something
that was kind of disturbing.
Like what?
How do you want to die?
[Hyera exhales softly]
You shouldn't meet him
even if he calls you again.
Okay.
If he contacts you,
please let me know.
[♪ music fades]
[Isoo] Hey, are you mad at me?
Who's more important to you,
me or the model?
It's been a while
since I found a model I liked, Isoo.
[sighs] Drink up.
Get inspiration from me today.
[clink]
- Hey, Seongwon.
- Yeah?
You said you met me when you were little.
- Yeah.
- When was that?
[sighs deeply] Seriously.
It annoys me that you don't remember,
so I'm not telling you.
At least give me a hint.
Back then,
you were a lot quieter than you are now.
You were shorter and thinner.
[♪ gentle, melancholy music playing]
The hallway was bright,
and a breeze was coming in
through the window.
SEO YUKYUNG PSYCHIATRIC CLINIC
It was quiet
and dull.
Surrounded by white walls,
it was the same thing day after day,
but then, you suddenly sat next to me.
Hey, what's your name?
What are you sick with?
How's my drawing?
It's really good.
Do you know what this is?
It's a puppy.
[door opens]
[Dr. Seo] Jin Isoo.
Come inside.
Jin Isoo.
[chuckles softly]
My picture.
Everyone said it was weird.
You were the only person
who complimented me.
Do you know why?
You recognized it
because you and I are alike.
In what way are we alike?
[exhales softly]
Your mom.
You said you were with her when she died.
[Seongwon] Huh?
How did it feel?
Did you witness the moment she died?
When her soul left her eyes?
That very moment?
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[door opens]
[door closes]
This is Detective Jin Isoo.
This is private investigator Jeong Minjae.
He used to work at Violent Crime with me.
Oh, it's nice to meet you.
You really helped us out today.
Not at all.
So, what did Areum say?
They met by chance,
and he asked her to be his model.
[Isoo] Hmm.
Did you talk to him?
He said I met him when I was young,
but I honestly don't remember.
What are you going to do now?
We'll have to keep watching.
He might go on a rampage
now that we've stopped him.
[Isoo sighs softly]
[sighs softly]
[footsteps approaching]
[crockery clinking]
[sighs wearily]
I bring Areum home...
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
- ...and he barges in an hour later?
- [car horn honking, blaring]
[scoffs softly]
That's strange.
Right?
[sighs deeply]
[♪ music fades]
[slurps]
[exhales deeply]
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
What the heck?
[sighs wearily]
[♪ music swells]
[sighs softly]
[♪ music fades]
Did Isoo...
side with Joo Hyera?
[♪ suspenseful sting]
[cell phone ringing over car audio]
DETECTIVE JOO HYERA
INCOMING CALL
[Hyera] Yu Seongwon found our cameras.
He destroyed them all.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
We have no way of watching him.
I'll look into it.
MR. CHOI
[line connects, ringing]
[Isoo] Mr. Choi, I have a favor to ask.
[engine revving]
HANSU AIR SPACE
[tires screeching]
[♪ music fades]
Ah, why did you come? I can go by myself.
I thought I might as well come see you.
How are you feeling?
- [inhales sharply]
- [exhales sharply]
It's a secret.
[whispering] How are you?
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
What did the hospital say?
They're going to monitor me for a while,
but I'm doing well so far.
[sighs in relief] That's such a relief.
What about you?
I'm taking medication and doing okay.
Really?
Really. You should
worry about yourself first.
[clicks tongue] Don't get sick.
- Right.
- Let's go.
[♪ upbeat, jaunty music playing]
Thank you all for your hard work.
Don't mind us. Please carry on.
It's been a while, Chief.
[♪ music fades]
Yes, please move it
right here.
[♪ quirky music playing]
What is it for?
Uh, you'll be in danger if you know.
Please set it up
so I can watch the live feed.
Please do as he says.
- [♪ music fades]
- So what exactly is this again?
- Mmm, a high-altitude UAV.
- [keyboard clacking]
A drone that can fly for a long time.
And it belongs to Hansu Group?
Yes. Some are supplied to the military,
others are used to monitor wildfires,
and one was in the air just for testing,
so I moved that one to Seongwon's studio.
Oh!
[Isoo] Four, three,
five, three, zero.
- [in English] Connect.
- [digital beeping]
[in Korean] It's live.
This should do, right?
[♪ upbeat swing jazz music playing]
Whoa.
I've never seen
such a cool chaebol before.
You're so cool, Detective Jin.
You've never seen a chaebol before?
It's no big deal.
Uh-uh. No, Jin Isoo.
You're impressive.
[all chuckling]
Really? This is nothing.
Honestly.
- [Minjae sighs]
- [♪ music fades]
If I was going to work
with someone like you,
I seriously wouldn't have quit.
How can you say that
when you quit after working with me?
Well, it's true.
Is there anything you can't do?
Not much, really. Mmm.
[chuckles]
This is a guy who buys an entire house
just because he wants to see the basement.
[♪ soft piano music playing in background]
[exhales incredulously] That's crazy.
Hyera, doesn't that give you
a huge dopamine rush?
- Is your brain okay?
- Every day is a roller coaster. Mmm.
The car we were driving blows up,
twin magicians show up.
That sounds so much fun. I'm jealous.
Join us. Come work for me.
Should I try joining the force again?
[chuckles]
- Hey, where are you going?
- The restroom.
[door opens]
- [sighs deeply]
- [door closes]
[Minjae] Thank you.
Kim Heejun's death
was a weight on her conscience.
And for me, too.
[♪ gentle, melancholy music playing]
Couldn't we have prevented it?
Was it maybe our fault?
I ran away from that like a coward,
while Hyera just endured it.
Saving Areum means a lot to us.
If it's with you, I think
we'll be able to catch Yu Seongwon.
Of course, we can, huh.
We'll catch that bastard
and isolate him from society for good.
- Cheers.
- [Minjae] Cheers.
- [Hyera] Hey, me too.
- [door closes]
[chuckles softly]
All right, let's do this.
- Let's do this!
[♪ music fades]
[groans]
God, my head. [sighs]
[sighs] I must be out of my mind.
[sighs wearily]
[chuckles] Roller coaster.
[grunts, groans]
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
[♪ music swells]
What's all this?
[♪ suspenseful, foreboding music playing]
[♪ music turns ominous]
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
[Younghwan laughing] Huh?
My friend, Jin Isoo. [laughs]
[Isoo] Younghwan, you, again!
You want to try, too?
No! Please... Don't!
I told you I'd never see you
if you did it again.
You should undergo
a proper investigation and quit drugs.
All my life,
I've never thought of you as a friend.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Jin Isoo.
[♪ music swells]
FLEX X COP 2
EPISODE 10
A BLOOD TRAIL SURROUNDS JIN ISOO
[♪ mellow emotional music playing]
Special Cast. Jeon Hyebin
What happened?
[Junyoung] He's Isoo's
middle school classmate.
Get a grip.
You have to remember something!
[detective] Jin Isoo, you're under arrest
for the murder of Kim Younghwan.
- You two fought, didn't you?
- Yes.
[Younghwan] Your friend
came to see you, punk.
You're finished.
I heard someone reported me.
[Isoo, over recording] I killed someone.
Got nothing left to deny?
[Hyera] They went in with a set narrative.
We're from Internal Affairs.
They found a high dose
of drugs in his system.
Does taking that drug
for the first time make you violent?
People with a lot
of pent-up anger tend to snap.
[Seongwon] Jin Isoo could be the killer.
Isoo! Maybe you've been holding it all in.
And it just blew up on Younghwan.
- [bang]
- Once you admit it,
you will be free.
[♪ song fades]
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
[Younghwan] Jin Isoo.
Goodbye.
[Younghwan laughing maniacally]
[squelch]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
Translated by Hyesoo Lee